你全身泡泡好可爱
You look cute in bubbles.
你喝太多眼花了
You're just all liquored up.
是我  我进去了
Hey, it's me. I'm coming in.
我今天上班累死了
I've had a very long, hard day.
我要去买炸鸡  你要不要
I'm gonna go get some chicken, you want some?
不了  谢谢  再见
No, thanks. No chicken. Bye-bye then.
你确定吗  炸鸡哦  再来点鸡杂饭和豆子
You sure? Some extra-crispy, dirty rice, bean?
我最后说一次我不要  出去  乔伊
For the last time, no! Get out, get out Joey!
知道了
All right.
你没事吧  抱歉  他死都不走
Are you okay?  I'm so sorry. He wouldn't leave.
缠着我问要不要炸鸡
He kept asking me if I wanted chicken.
炸鸡
Chicken?
来点炸鸡也不错
I could eat some chicken.
乔伊
Hey, Joy.
我要三块鸡  沙拉  豆子和可乐
Could I get a three-piece, some coleslaw, some beans and a Coke?
健怡可乐
Diet Coke.
-早安  菲比  -我非告诉你们不可
- Morning, Pheebs. - I have to tell you this story.
刚才载我来的计程车司机...
I was coming over and this cabdriver...
那人是不是叫安格斯
Was his name Angus?
什么
What?
我们在伦敦碰到的计程车司机
He was a cabdriver we had in London.
好吧  总之
All right. Anyway...
他载我们去的酒吧叫什么来着
What was the place that pub he took us to?
麦子酒吧
The Wheat Sheaf!
对  那里有一种啤酒
Yeah! And they had that beer...
柏丁顿
Boddingtors!
菲比有话要说
Pheebs was going to tell a story.
他的帽子很好笑...
Yeah, okay. So he had a really funny hat.
我不想说了
I don't want to talk about it.
-嘿  -嘿  罗斯
- Hey. - Hey, Ross!
柏丁顿
Boddingtors!
老天
Oh, man!
那啤酒真好喝
That was good beer.
若是能再喝一杯  要我走回伦敦都行
I'd walk back to London for another frosty one of those bad boys.
世贸附近的英国酒吧里
You know, I think they have those at the British pub
-好像就有  -回头见
- by the Trade Center. - Later!
瑞秋不是应该回来了吗
Isn't Rachel suppose be back by now?
可是班机在雅典误点了
Yeah, but her plane got delayed at Athens.
不过现在也该到了
But acutally she should be here by now.
你跟她通过电话了  她很生气吗
So you talked to her? Did she sound mad?
不会  那是因为她喜欢我
No. But she likes me.
你把她丢在了前往希腊的飞机上
You abandoned her on a plane to Greece.
我才没有丢下瑞秋  懂吗
Okay, I did not "abandon" Rachel. Okay?
艾蜜莉出现在机场
Emily showed up at the airport.
我当然得去追她  我别无选择
I had to go after her. I mean I did what I had to do.
她是我妻子  瑞秋是我妻子
She's my wife. Rachel is my wife.
艾蜜莉
Emily!
艾蜜莉是我妻子
Emily is my wife.
我是怎么了
Man, what is that?
你还没有艾蜜莉的消息吗
So you still haven't heard from Emily?
我在机场追丢之后就没有了
No, not since I lost her at the airport.
她竟然跑得比你快
I can't believe she can outrun you.
她是飞毛腿  好吗
Hey! She's fast, okay?
你自以为比我厉害吗
You think you can beat me?
咱们现在就去外头较量
Let's go! Outside!
-嗨  -我的天  瑞秋
- Hi! - Oh, my God, Rachel!
瑞秋  我很抱歉  非常非常抱歉
Rach, Rach, I am so sorry. I am so, so sorry.
罗斯  别这样  你没做错
Ross, come on. You just did what you had to do.
嗨  菲比
Hi, Pheebs.
就这样  你不生气吗  肯定是糟糕透了
That's it? You're not mad? It must've been terrible.
糟糕透了  我可是在希腊
Terrible? Hell, I was in Greece!
那间酒店非常棒  海滩很美  人又和善
There was a nice hotel, nice beach, met the nice people.
对我瑞秋来说可不差
It's not too shabby for Rachel.
就这样吗  不生气吗
So, what, that's it?
是的
Oh yeah.
没事  我没生你的气
We're cool. Totally cool.
谢谢  瑞秋  你真好
Thanks, Rach. You're the best.
不  你才好呢
Oh, no. You're the best.
我要去花店一趟
Oh, I got to go to the flower store.
听着  大家都不肯说艾蜜莉在哪里
Check it out, no one will tell me where Emily is...
我决定寄72朵长茎红玫瑰到艾蜜莉父母家
So I'm gonna send 72 long-stemmed, red roses to her parents' house.
代表我认识并且深爱她的72天
One for each day that I've known and loved her.
她一定会被感动的
That ought get her talking to me again.
罗斯  写卡片时别忘了
Ross, when you make out the card,
对方是  艾蜜莉
be sure to make it out to "Emily."
太好了  幸好你在希腊玩得开心
That's great, it's so good that you had such a good time in Greece.
什么
What?
我在希腊才不开心
I didn't have a good time in Greece!
罗斯丢下我一个人  懂吗
Ross abandoned me! Okay?
我买不到机票回来
I couldn't get a plane out.
只好待在他们的蜜月套房
I had to stay in their honeymoon suite!
每个人都过来问我
With people coming up to me all the time going,
盖勒太太  你哭什么
"Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?"
简直丢死人了
I mean, it was so humiliating!
我真是个白痴
I felt like such an idiot!
这都是我的错  你们知道为什么吗
I mean it's all my fault. You know why?
因为我的决定都不对
Because I make very bad decisions.
-不是这样的  -是的
- Oh, that's not true. - Yes it is.
就是这样  我跑去蠢伦敦追罗斯
It is true. I went after Ross in stupid London!
伦敦的确是个蠢地方
London is stupid! Stupid!
菲比  你说得对  我根本不该去伦敦
Phoebe, you were right. I should've never gone to London.
从现在开始  由你帮我做决定
From now on, you make all my decisions for me.
不行  我以前就这么做过
Oh, no. I did that for someone once.
我不喜欢主宰别人的生活
I'm not comfortable having that kind of power control someone's life.
那我来
I'll do it.
很好
That's fine.
莫妮卡  以后由你主宰我的感情生活
So Monica, you are now in charge of my love life.
我该去上班了
Okay. I got to go to work.
瑞秋  很高兴看到你回来
And Rachel, great to have you back.
菲比
Pheebs!
看到你真开心
Always a pleasure.
瑞秋  亲爱的  你看
Rachel? Sweetie, look.
你和乔伊在婚宴上的照片拍得多好
Here's a really cute picture of you and Joey at reception.
他已经结婚了
He's married.
罗斯结婚了  我到现在还不敢相信
Ross is married. I still can't believe it.
亲爱的  抓旁边就好
Honey, sweetie, by the edges.
看来我只好接受事实
I'll just have to accept it.
这都要怪我
I mean, it's my fault.
别抓中间  指纹会弄脏照片
Sweetie! Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!
天啊
Oh, my God!
算了  算了
That's okay. That's okay.
我知道你心情低落
I know that you're very upset right now, okay?
我知道你不是故意找我麻烦
I know that wasn't about me.
我看她就是跟她作对
I bet it was about her a little.
你要是肯放下罗斯一分钟
If you'd stop thinking about Ross for on minute...
就会发现到处都有好男人
...you'd notice there are great guys everywhere.
你看  比如说甘瑟
Look. Gunther. I mean...
他既善良又可爱
He's nice. He's cute.
是啊  甘瑟的确...
Yeah. I guess Gunther is...
还有那边那个家伙
What about that guy over there?
你以前跟他在吧台还打情骂俏过呢
That's the guy you flirted with at the counter that time.
我不知道...
Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
你现在就去跟他说话
You're going to talk to him.
我们说好了  我为你做决定
We made a deal. I make your decisions,
我命令你去跟他说话
and I say you're going to talk to him.
好吧
All right.
你说了算  看来我只好照办
You're the boss. Guess I got to do what you tell me.
他听到这句话肯定上钩
Say that to him, and you're golden.
菲比
Hey, Phoebe.
嗨  菲比  我们在伦敦的照片洗出来了
Hey, Pheebs. We got our pictures back from London.
这张是所有人在伦敦塔拍的
Here's all of us at the Tower of London...
大家都在照片中
Here we all are.
有罗斯  乔伊  你
There's Ross and Joey and you and...
还有我
And me.
你一定听烦我们说伦敦的事了
You know what, we've been talking about London too much, haven't we?
是我不好  因为我去不了
No, I'm sorry, it's just because I couldn't be there.
我只能大着肚子  烦都快烦死了
All I get to do now is pregnant stuff. It bums me out.
-对不起  -对不起
- I'm sorry. - Sorry.
-怎么样  -总之我们东扯西扯
- What happened? - You know, a little of this, a little of that.
明天晚上我要出去约会
I got myself a date tomorrow night.
看吧  我就说吧  你已经忘记罗斯了
See? Didn't I tell you? You're getting over Ross already.
滚出去
Get out.
怎么这么晚才回来
What took you so long?
公事耽搁了  不过我明天就辞职
I got caught up at work. But I'm quitting tomorrow.
谢谢你邀我过来
So thanks for having me over.
瑞秋
Rach.
菲比
Pheebs.
再见  哥们
See you, man.
他发什么神经
What the hell was that?
可能是在伦敦学到的欧洲告别风俗
Probably some European goodbye thing he picked up in London.
那才不是欧洲风俗
That's not European.
比较像法式热吻
It felt French.
我玩得好开心
God, I really had a good time.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me too.
看来今天要结束了
So, I guess this is it.
是啊
Yeah.
除非你想进来
Unless you want to come inside?
-好啊  -好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
等等  我无法自作主张
Wait a minute. You know what? I can't decide this.
-好了  等我一下  -好的
- Okay. Just hold on a second, okay. - Yeah.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
莫妮卡在吗  我有事要问她
Is Monica around? I have to ask her something.
她去洗衣服了
Doing her laundry.
那是什么
What's that?
我今天收到的包裹
It came in the mail today, it's...
72朵长茎红玫瑰
72 long-stemmed red roses.
代表我认识艾蜜莉并且深爱她的72天
One for each day I've known and loved Emily...
给剪成碎片了
...cut up into mulch.
亲爱的  真是糟糕
Honey, that's awful.
还好啦
It's not so bad.
莫妮卡要用来做香料
Monica's going to make potpourri.
我要去淋雨散散心
I think I'm going to go wander out in the rain for a while.
外面没下雨
It's not raining.
连老天都不赏脸
I can't catch a break!
知道吗  罗斯  你哪里也别去
You know what Ross? You're not going anywhere.
就坐这里
You're gonna sit right here.
我为你泡杯好茶  我们好好聊聊
I'll make you a cup of tea and we'll talk this out.
好吗
All right?
好的
Okay.
嗨  大卫
Hey, Dave.
改天再请你进来  我的室友病得很重
Listen, I need to take a rain check. My roommate is really sick.
再见
Okay. Bye!
亲爱的  听着
Honey, listen.
老天  我知道事情看起来很糟
I know, God, I know things seem so bad right now...
-瑞秋  -而且不会...
- Rach? - ...and that they won't get any...
我可以跟你谈谈吗
Could I talk to you just for a minute?
我掉了几只袜子
I dropped some socks.
好的
Yeah.
你哪根筋不对  你又想自找苦吃吗
What is the matter with you? Do you want to fall into the trap?
你又想自找苦吃吗
Do you want to fall into the trap?
你根本没掉袜子
You did not drop any socks!
我刚碰到大卫  他说你打发他走
I just run into Dave, and he told me you blew him off!
你给我听好
You listen to me!
这里由我当家
I'm calling the shots!
我要你离开罗斯去追大卫
I say you leave Ross alone and go get Dave.
你到底想怎么样
What the hell are you trying to do?
其实我想  我打算
Well, ultimately I was trying, you know, I wanted...
告诉他我还爱他
...to tell him that I'm still in love with him.
什么  你不能说
What? You cannot tell him that!
为什么  为什么不行
Why? Why not?
大家都喜欢听到这种话
People love to hear that!
这里由我做决定  我不准你说
I make the decisions and I say no!
知道吗  你不能帮我做决定  因为
You know what? No, you don't make my decisions, because...
你被解雇了
...you're fired.
你不能解雇我
You can't fire me.
你的事情由我来决定
I make your decisions,
我决定  我没被解雇
and I say I'm not fired! Ha!
既然如此
Well...
瑞秋  让我进去
Rachel, come on, let me in!
有麻烦吗
Having some trouble?
瑞秋把我锁在门外
Rachel locked the door.
你肯亲我  我就帮你撞开
I'll kick that door in if you give me some sugar.
瑞秋  开门
Rachel, let me in.
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋  我们出去谈谈好吗
Rachel? Can I talk to you outside for a sec?
不好
No.
我真的有话要跟你说
I really need to talk to you.
那就说啊
Well, then talk.
那我就说了
Okay, I will.
记得我们刚才讨论的  你要做的事吗
Remember that thing we just discussed that you wanted to do?
-记得  -什么事
- Yes. - What thing?
是这样
Well...
瑞秋要去上摇摆舞班
Rachel wants to take swing dance lessons.
我觉得是个蠢主意
Which I think is a really stupid idea.
很危险  她的目的永远达不到
It's dangerous. She's never going to get what she wants.
而且搞不好她还会伤到人
And who knows who she might end up hurting?
莫妮卡说得对  摇摆舞是有点危险
Monica's right. Swing dancing can be tricky.
我要打个电话
I'm gonna use the phone.
取消五只送给艾蜜莉的熊宝宝
I gotta cancel those five giant teddy bears I sent to Emily.
否则熊宝宝难逃死劫
My God! Think of the massacre.
我就是要说
I'm gonna do it.
瑞秋  我知道你认为我疯了
Rachel, okay. I know you think I'm crazy.
但是在你告诉他之前
Please before you tell him you love him,
至少找到一个
just try to find one person...
支持你的人  我打赌你找不到
...who thinks it's a good idea. Because I bet you can't.
-但我...  -拜托
- But I... - Please?
好吧
All right. Fine.
乔伊  我已经进来了
Joey! I'm in!
那敢情好
All right. Good deal.
-菲比  -嘿  菲比
- Pheebs! - Hey, Pheebs.
-菲比  -什么事
- Okay, Pheebs? - Yeah.
那天你说
You know how the other day you were talking about
你不能去伦敦
how you didn't get to go to London...
-觉得自己被大家遗弃了  -是的
- ...and you were feeling left out? - Yeah.
我们很愧疚  所以
Well, we all felt really bad about that... So,
我们决定大家一起去旅行
we decided we should all take a little trip together!
太好了
Oh, that's so nice!
太好了  要去哪里
How great! Where's the trip?
我们可以一起去野餐
Well, we thought we would all go to a picnic...
就去中央公园
...in Central Park!
中央  公园
Central Park?
大家一起去个一整天
All of us. All day.
什么鸟地方
That sucks!
那根本不算旅行  我刚从公园过来
That's not a trip! I just came from the park.
烂中央公园有什么值得击掌庆祝的
What'll we gonna high-five about at the stupid Central Park?
好耶  就在我家旁边
It's right by my house. All right!
我决定回家反省这个烂主意
I'm going home to bask in the triumph of my Central Park idea.
等一下  热吻先生
Hold on a sec there, Mr. Kissy.
我一直想跟你讨论
You know I've been meaning to talk to you about...
你新学的欧洲风情
...this whole little new European thing you've got going on.
我要告诉你  你让我非常不自在
And I just need to tell you it makes me very uncomfortable...
拜托你别再亲了
...and I just, you know, just stop it!
我只是想给大家介绍下欧洲文化
I just trying to bringing a little culture to the group.
行啊  只要不介绍到我嘴里就好了
That's fine. Just don't bring it in my mouth.
我都快吐了
It makes me want to puke.
各位  菲比来了
Hey, everybody! Pheebs is here!
-菲比  -菲比来了
- Phoebe! - Hey, Pheebs.
大家好啊
Okay. Woo! Hi!
菲比  我们认为野餐的主意有点...
Okay. Pheebs, we decided that the picnic idea was a little...
不太...  实在烂透了
It didn't have any... Well, it blew.
所以
So...
我们决定今天下午
We thought that this afternoon
大家一起去度周末
we'd all go away for the whole weekend...
到大西洋城去
...to Atlantic City.
大西洋城  太好了  谁的主意
Atlantic City! Oh, that's a great plan! Whose plan was that?
我的
Mine!
-等等  是我提议的  -错
- Wait. It was my plan. - No...
我说我们应该想个新的计划
...I said we needed a new plan.
然后我想到要去大西洋城
And I came up with Atlantic City.
这就是新的计划啊
Which is the new plan.
大家一小时后楼上见吧
Okay, why don't we all meet upstairs in an hour.
好的
Okay.
我要去打包了  我要摇着大屁股好好打包
I'm going to go pack. I'm going to go pack my ass off.
瑞秋  我们走吧
Come on, Rachel, let's go.
我等会上去找你
You know what? I'm gonna meet you upstairs in a minute.
瑞秋  没有人支持你  所以你不能说
No. Rachel, you didn't find anyone, so you can't tell him.
知道吗  无所谓
You know what? That doesn't matter.
瑞秋
Okay, Rachel.
你知道对方不能
Do you have any idea know how painful it is
回应你的爱意  你会有多痛苦吗
to tell someone you love them and not have them say it back?
我不在乎
I don't care.
好吧
Okay.
我可看不下去
I can't watch.
你在看什么
What you reading?
报纸
Paper.
上面说了什么
Yeah? What's it about?
世界各地的新闻
Events from around the globe.
好吧
Okay.
罗斯  听我说
Ross you know what,
我得告诉你一件事
there's something I have to talk to you about.
虽然大家都叫我别说
Everyone's been saying I shouldn't tell you.
但我觉得他们都错了  是人就会犯错
But I think they're wrong. You know how people can be wrong.
当然了  有一次上班时
Sure. Once at work...
我说放射性碳测定法太过时了
...I thought carbon dating is fossilized...
罗斯  我说正经的
Okay, Ross, I'm really trying to tell you something here.
说吧
Go ahead.
我这就说了
I think I'm just going to say it.
现在就告诉你
I'm just going to say it.
我还爱着你  罗斯
I'm still in love with you, Ross.
我不知道现在该怎么回答
I'm not sure what to do with that right now.
怎么了  你跟我开玩笑吗  那就太恶劣了
What? Was that a joke? Because it's mean.
我很正经
I'm so dead serious!
不能再正经了
I'm totally serious!
那你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
因为我刚听到自己的话
Because I just heard it!
我听到了  而且觉得很荒谬
I heard it. And it's ridiculous!
我是说
I mean...
你已经结婚了
You're married!
你结婚了  太荒谬了  就像...
You're married, and it's just ridiculous! It's like...
我说话的时候  似乎灵魂出窍了
When I said it, I sort of floated up out of my body.
然后我的灵魂听到肉身说话
And then I heard myself say it, and then the floating Rachel...
灵魂认为自己实在很白痴
I was like, "You are such an idiot!"
-我的确已经结婚了  -我知道
- Well, I am married. - I know.
虽然婚礼后就没跟老婆说过话
Even though I haven't spoken to my wife since the wedding.
抱歉  这不好笑
I'm sorry. That's not funny.
其实还蛮好笑的
Actually, it kind of is.
我老婆不回我电话
My wife won't return my calls.
我不知道我老婆在哪里
I don't know where my wife is.
"罗斯  你老婆呢"  我也不知道
"Hey, Ross! Where's the missus?" "Don't know!"
天啊
Oh, God!
好了
Okay.
你觉得你可以
You know what? Do you think...
忘记我刚说的话吗
Do you think you could just forget that I told you this?
我不忘记也不行
Well, I kind of have to.
因为事实是
I mean because the thing is...
事实就是你已经娶了艾蜜莉
The thing is, you know, that you're married to Emily.
事实正是如此
That is what the thing is.
天啊
Oh, God.
罗斯  我们还是好朋友吧
Ross, things won't be weird between us, right?
我说自己还爱你  真是太蠢了
I mean it was such a stupid thing me telling you that?
不会  我很高兴你告诉我
No, no! I'm glad you did.
别的不说
Look if nothing else...
总之听到有人说爱你都会很开心的
...it's always great when someone tells you they love you.
我也是这么说的
That's what I said!
罗斯  谢谢你对我这么好
Ross, thank you for being so nice.
我才该谢谢你
No. Thank you for...
谢谢你
Thank you.
-大家走吧  -向大西洋城出发
- Okay, let's go! - Yeah, Atlantic City!
走吧
Come on!
去大西洋城哦
Atlantic City, baby!
我们去好好扔扔骰子  乔伊
Let's roll some bones. Hey, Joey!
为扔骰子击个掌
High-five for rolling bones.
菲比  你在漏水
Pheebs, you're leaking.
天啊  你羊水破了
Oh, my God! Your water broke!
哦  是啊
Oh, okay.
别放在心上  我要坐前座
Well, don't worry. I call shotgun.
菲比  我们得送你去医院
Pheebs, we have to take you to the hospital now.
菲比  菲比
Pheebs, Pheebs.
你快要生了
the babies are coming now.
亲爱的  击掌  你要生了
Honey! High-five! The babies are coming!
记不记得我的羊水什么时候破的
Remember when my water broke?
真不敢相信  菲比竟然快生了
I can't believe Phoebe's going to have her babies!
我知道  真是太棒了
I know. It's beautiful and amazing.
知道还有什么我也不敢相信吗
You know else I can't believe.
竟然每次离开  我都得亲菲比和瑞秋
I had to kiss Phoebe and Rachel every time I left the room.
可惜她们没看到我们上床
It's too bad they didn't see us having sex.
你到底了不了解女人
Do you know anything about women?
不了解
No.
-算了  -好的
- It's all right. - Okay.